revenuecentral.net 2016-06-20

# revenuecentral.net

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy policy regards how revenuecentral.net (“Site” or “RevenueCentral”) stores and deals with information we collect from you (“Member”).

By signing up and using RevenueCentral you will agree to have read, understood, and accepted the following terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any of these terms, you must not register and use Site.

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through the Site.

RevenueCentral reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time and impose changes without prior notification of its Members. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. You agree and acknowledge that you will review this Privacy Policy on a regular basis and in the event of a change to it terms and conditions, you will continue using this Site following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of such changes.

**What Information We Collect?**

We collect Member’s personal information when he / she registers on the Site and fills out profile on their account. While signing up and using the site Member must submit the following personal information: full name, sex, email address, date of birth, email address / ID of payment processor’s account. You should also create a unique username and password (optionally secondary password).

**Why We Collect Your Personal Information?**

We collect your personal information:

• to create and support your account;

• to communicate with you;

• to personalize your experience;

• to prevent unauthorized access to your account;

• to improve the Site and customer service;

• to process transactions;

• to send periodic emails.

**How Your Personal Information Is Protected?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do We Use Cookies?**

We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies. We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.

Cookies will only be used to store your preferences.

Your browser must accept cookies. You are always free to decline our cookies.

**Can Any Of Your Personal Information Be Disclosed To Third Parties?**

All Member’s personal information, financial reports, messages and other info displayed and / or stored by RevenueCentral are of private nature, and will not be disclosed to third parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating the Site, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release Members personally information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce the Site policies, or protect our and / or Member(s) and / or others rights, property or safety.

Non-personally identifiable Member’s information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**_April 13, 2016_**
